Jay, [music] as you can see, uh, I'm
currently a full-time employee, and
while I earn enough [music]
for my future, top of mind, I think
Sunlife Secure Income will fit you. H, I
see.
[music] Insurance? Nope. More than that,
it's a plan that gives you guaranteed
[music] insurance protection and yearly
cash payout for life. Imagine every year
you will get extra funds from your
policy. Funds that you can use for life
goals [music] like uh starting your own
business or building your travel funds.
>> I see. You know, I [music] can always
use extra money per uh lifetime.
Lifetime ba talaga.
>> We say lifetime, we mean it. At the
[music] end of your six-year policy,
you'll get guaranteed lifetime yearly
payouts equal to 6% of the face amount.
And I tell you that's currently the
highest payout [music] rate in the
market.
>> As in yearly
h what if I live really really long?
>> Your income never stops. You'll get cash
[music] payouts until the age 100
centinarian bonus.
>> Wow, that sounds amazing. [music]
Um,
absolutely. We have manageable payments.
You can pay yearly, quarterly, even
monthly. [music] It is also very
convenient to settle your payments.
>> I see. Well, I [music] guess this is the
plan that I need. What do I need to get
started?
>> That's why I'm here.
Talk to a Sunlife advisor today.